<resources>

    <string name="app_name">XYZ Reader</string>
    <string name="welcome_xyz_reader">Welcome to XYZ Reader!</string>

    <string name="action_refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_share">Share</string>

    <string name="up">Up</string>
    <string name="temp_body">For starters, let me try to summarize the lessons and intuitions\r\nI\'ve had about ebooks from my release of two novels and most of a\r\nshort story collection online under a Creative Commons license. A\r\nparodist who published a list of alternate titles for the\r\npresentations at this event called this talk, \"eBooks Suck Right\r\nNow,\" [eBooks suck right now] and as funny as that is, I don\'t\r\nthink it\'s true.\r\n\r\nNo, if I had to come up with another title for this talk, I\'d\r\ncall it: \"Ebooks: You\'re Soaking in Them.\" [Ebooks: You\'re\r\nSoaking in Them] That\'s because I think that the shape of ebooks\r\nto come is almost visible in the way that people interact with\r\ntext today, and that the job of authors who want to become rich\r\nand famous is to come to a better understanding of that shape.\r\n\r\nI haven\'t come to a perfect understanding. I don\'t know what the\r\nfuture of the book looks like. But I have ideas, and I\'ll share\r\nthem with you:\r\n\r\n1. Ebooks aren\'t marketing. [Ebooks aren\'t marketing] OK, so\r\nebooks *are* marketing: that is to say that giving away ebooks\r\nsells more books. Baen Books, who do a lot of series publishing,\r\nhave found that giving away electronic editions of the previous\r\ninstallments in their series to coincide with the release of a\r\nnew volume sells the hell out of the new book -- and the\r\nbacklist. And the number of people who wrote to me to tell me\r\nabout how much they dug the ebook and so bought the paper-book\r\nfar exceeds the number of people who wrote to me and said, \"Ha,\r\nha, you hippie, I read your book for free and now I\'m not gonna\r\nbuy it.\" But ebooks *shouldn\'t* be just about marketing: ebooks\r\nare a goal unto themselves. In the final analysis, more people\r\nwill read more words off more screens and fewer words off fewer\r\npages and when those two lines cross, ebooks are gonna have to be\r\nthe way that writers earn their keep, not the way that they\r\npromote the dead-tree editions.\r\n\r\n2. Ebooks complement paper books. [Ebooks complement paper\r\nbooks]. </string>

</resources>
